brastelremit.jp 2018-04-12

# Legal information - Brastel Remit Remittance Service

## General Principles

BRASTEL Co., Ltd. (hereafter referred to as "BRASTEL" including BRASTEL REMIT) is committed to safeguard your information. By 'your information' we mean any information about you that you or third parties provide to us. We hereby declare: we shall handle your information strictly according to the following terms as well as relevant laws and regulations. This policy will be continuously revised to strengthen the security of your information.

## 1\. Collection and Handling of Private Information

It is our principle to collect and use your information in a fair and legitimate manner. The collection and use of your information will be practiced in compliance with Act on the Protection of Personal Information, solely for the provision of our Services in relation to overseas money transfer (hereafter collectively referred to as "Services") unless otherwise required by law or exigencies.

### 1.1 Collection

(1) BRASTEL shall neither obtain private information by fraudulence or other similar means nor use the information obtained by such means.

(2) We shall state or indicate purpose of use before collecting your information.

### 1.2 Purpose of Use

BRASTEL REMIT uses your information solely for the provision of the Services. Listed below is how we handle the information internally (see Section 2 as for its disclosure to trusted third parties). You will be notified if there is any change to the purposes of use listed below. We use your information for:

(a) Opening your BRASTEL REMIT deposit account and providing you with the Services.  
(b) Verifying your or your designated representative's identity in compliance with Act on Prevention of Transfer of Criminal Proceeds.  
(c) Administration of your account, such as sending you transaction reports and due date notices, answering your inquiries and providing you with other services regarding your account management.  
(d) Assessing feasibility of transaction.  
(e) Exercising our rights and fulfilling our obligations in accordance with the Terms and Conditions together with relevant laws and regulations.  
(f) Market research, data analysis and questionnaires for improving our Services.  
(g) Assessing risk in transaction and conducting inspections both internally and externally.  
(h) Accounting and tax payment.  
(I) When there arises a dispute between you and BRASTEL.  
(k) Cancellation of transaction and subsequent procedures.  
(l) Other purposes to make the dealings between you and BRASTEL beneficial.

## 2\. Disclosure of Private Information

Brastel shall in no way disclose your information to any third party without your prior consent unless otherwise required by the Personal Information Protection Law (also referred to in Section 4) and other relevant regulations. In this section we describe the conditions on which we may share your information with someone outside BRASTEL.

### 2.1 Personal Information Protection Law

As stipulated in the Law we may provide private information to a third party when:  
(a) Required by laws and regulations (to share the information with relevant authorities, including external inspection).  
(b) Such information is necessary for protecting the life, body or property of any person but it is difficult to obtain user consent.  
(c) The information is necessary for improving public health or promoting the sound growth of children but it is difficult to obtain user consent.  
(d) In cooperation with State agencies or local governments or their delegates in practicing the affairs prescribed by laws and regulations and such a performance is likely to be impeded by obtaining user consent.

### 2.2 Trusted Contractor

We may opt for outsourcing in relation to our Services which necessitates us to provide your information to an individual or corporate contractor. In such a case we shall choose a suitable contractor and continuously ensure that your information is handled with high standards of security. The main purposes of sharing your information with our trusted contractor is:  
(a) To provide the Services effectively and comprehensively.  
(b) For co-management of risks and business operations.  
(c) For joint-marketing.  
(d) For co-promotion of mutual products and services.

### 2.3 Data to Share

When BRASTEL agrees to share private information with a third party, we generally disclose your name and address, telephone/fax number, email address, deposit account number and occupation.

### 2.4 Sensitive Information

In order to maintain fair and effective business operations, we may collect sensitive information such as; political affiliations, religion, creed, lineage, permanent address, trade union membership, racial background, medical record, sexual orientation, criminal record and so on. All sensitive information shall be handled according to Guidelines on Personal Information Protection in the Financial Industry (Financial Services Agency: Notification 67, 2004) and never be collected, used nor shared with any third party unless otherwise required by law or other exigencies.

## 3\. Administration of Private Information

In order to administer your information securely, BRASTEL designates an Information Officer (IO) per each division and branch pursuant to applicable laws; takes three types of security measures - Organisational, Operational and Technical. Information leakage, for instance, shall be prevented by our devising appropriate security measures against unauthorised access, computer virus and other security threats.

3.1 BRASTEL is committed to keeping your information accurate and up to date.  
3.2 We are responsible for the management of your information. Please contact our Customer Service for any inquiry or complaint regarding information security.

## 4\. Applicable Laws and Regulations

Your information is handled in compliance with relevant laws, guidelines and other regulations. For your reference, we list below the principle ones among these.  
(a) Act on the Protection of Personal Information (Act No. 57 of May 30, 2003).  
(b) Basic Policy on the Protection of Personal Information (Cabinet Order of April 2004).  
(c) Guidelines on Personal Information Protection in the Financial Industry (Financial Services Agency: Notification of December 2004).  
(d) Manual on Security Measures in Guidelines on Personal Information Protection in the Financial Industry (Financial Services Agency: Notification of January 2005).

## 5\. Inquiry, Request and Complaint

You are required to follow necessary procedures for a records inquiry, amendment, deletion and termination regarding your information.

5.1 BRASTEL respects your privacy and accepts your requests in relation to retained information*, such as records inquiry, notification of usage, amendment, deletion or discontinuation and termination of provision to a third party.  
(*In Act on the Protection of Personal Information, it is referred to as: "such personal data over which a business operator handling personal information has the authority to disclose, correct, add or delete the content, discontinue its utilization, erase, and discontinue its provision to a third party.")

5.2 If you receive email, phone or mail communications from us that you prefer not to receive, you may opt-out from receiving these communications simply by notifying us. We will process your request upon successful ID verification.

5.3 Please contact our Customer Service for any inquiry, request or complaint regarding our private policy and handling of your information. We will try our best to give you a quick response. If your request or complaint results in an investigation, it will be conducted without delay.

BRASTEL REMIT Customer Service  
2-6-2 Yokoami Sumida-ku, Tokyo 130-0015  
Tel: 0120-983-891 / 03-6869-4851  
Mon.-Fri.: 9:30 to 18:30 / Sat.: 10:00 to 18:00  
Email: english@brastelremit.jp

## 6\. Internal Control

BRASTEL is committed to complying with relevant laws and regulations as well as keeping its internal control at the highest standards in order that your information is handled correctly and securely.

6.1 We shall safeguard your information by:  
(a) Making this Private Policy public.  
(b) Enacting User Information Security Rules.  
(c) Directing all our employees and contractors to comply with the above Policy and Rules.

6.2 The Chief Information Officer (CIO) designates an Information Officer (IO) in each division and branch in order that we shall comprehensively devise and renew all possible measures to secure your information.
